Guide to the Asa and Elna Spaulding Papers, 1909-1997 and undated, bulk 1935-1983 RL.01240
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Asa Spaulding Subgroup, 1909-1984 and undated, 331 boxes
  - Organizations Series, 1930-1983 and undated, bulk 1954-1970, 145 boxes
    - Bowles and Tillinghast, Inc.,1964 and undated (Box AO-15)
    - Boy Scouts of America,1947-1950 (Box AO-15)
    - Boy Scouts of America,1957-1967 (Box AO-16)
    - Boyden International Group, Inc.,1970-1979, 4 folders (Box AO-16)
    - Boys' Clubs of America, Inc.,1947-1983, Folder 1 of 5 (Box AO-16)
    - Boys' Clubs of America, Inc.,1947-1983, Folders 2-5 of 5 (Box AO-17)
    - Bureau of Government Research,1969 (Box AO-17)
    - Burlington Industries,1980 (Box AO-18)
    - Business Committee for the Arts,1967-1970 (Box AO-18)
    - Business Development Corporation of North Carolina (BDCNC),1982 (Box AO-18)
    - Business Week Reports to Executives on Public Relations for Industry (Box AO-18)
    - Camp Graham DevelopmentโDurham County,1959 (Box AO-18)
    - Campbell University,1971-1980 (Box AO-18)
    - Capital Formation, Inc.,1970 (Box AO-18)
    - Carolina Friends School,1965-1966 (Box AO-18)
    - Carolina Population Center,1971 (Box AO-18)
    - Carte Blanche,1965 (Box AO-18)
    - Center for Human Relations Concerns of Business,1974 (Box AO-18)
    - Center for International Management Studies,1971 (Box AO-18)
    - Center for Urban Studies, University of Miami,1971 (Box AO-18)
    - Century Mark Association of America,1960-1965 (Box AO-18)
    - Chain Investment Corporation,1965-1966 (Box AO-18)
    - Challenge, Inc.,1969-1970 (Box AO-18)
    - Chamber of Commerce of the United States,1950-1968 and undated, Folder 1 of 18 (Box AO-18)
    - Chamber of Commerce of the United States,1950-1968 and undated Mar., Folders 2-8 of 18 (Box AO-19)
    - Chamber of Commerce of the United States,1950-1968 and undated June, Folders 9-15 of 18 (Box AO-20)
    - Chamber of Commerce of the United States,1950-1968 and undated, Folders 16-18 of 18 (Box AO-21)
    - Chicago Daily Defender Round Table of Commerce,1964-1967 (Box AO-21)
    - Chicago Urban League. General,1957-1968 (Box AO-21)
    - Chicago Urban League. Printed Material,1958-1968 (Box AO-21)
    - Chicago Urban League. Official Reports and Statements,1959-1965, 2 folders (Box AO-22)
    - Child Advocacy Commission of Durham,1980 (Box AO-22)
    - Christian Higher Education Challenge,1960-1962 (Box AO-22)
    - Chrysler Corporation,1969 (Box AO-22)
    - Churches. Programs,1960-1982 (Box AO-22)
      See separate entry in this series for materials on White Rock Baptist Church.
    - Citation Photo Industries, Inc.,1983 (Box AO-22)
    - Citizens' Advisory Committee,1962-1965 (Box AO-22)
    - Citizens' Committee for Children of New York, Inc.,1968 (Box AO-22)
    - Citizens' Committee to Promote Passage of Constitutional Amendment,1970 (Box AO-22)
    - City Club of New York,1972 (Box AO-22)
    - City College of New York,1967 (Box AO-22)
    - City of Durham,1964 (Box AO-22)
    - Clean Community Systems of Durham,1982 (Box AO-22)
    - Cleland Committee,1974 (Box AO-22)
    - College of Agricultural Sciences,1983 (Box AO-22)
    - College Foundation, Inc.,1964 (Box AO-22)
    - Colored Orphanage of North Carolina,1942-1958 (Box AO-22)
    - Columbus County Agricultural Conservation Association,1939-1944 (Box AO-22)
    - Committee for Economic Development,1962-1968, 5 folders (Box AO-23)
    - Committee for the Establishment of a Black Cultural Arts Center in North Carolina,1978 (Box AO-23)
    - Committee on State and Local Government Cooperation,1971 (Box AO-23)
    - Committee on State and Local Government Cooperation,1971, 2 folders (Box AO-24)
    - Committee to Study Financing for Industrial Development,1962 (Box AO-24)
    - Committee in Support of United Forces for Education Proposals,1967 (Box AO-24)
    - Common Cause,1970-1971 and undated, 2 folders (Box AO-24)
    - Community Chest,1940-1944 (Box AO-24)
    - Community Health Organization Committee,1964 (Box AO-24)
    - Community Planning Council,1963 (Box AO-24)
    - Community, Regional and Natural Resources Development Group Committee,1966-1967 (Box AO-24)
    - Community Service Bureau,1963 (Box AO-24)
    - Conference of Actuaries in Public Practice,1949-1964 (Box AO-24)
    - Conference on Cities,1971, Folder 1 of 2 (Box AO-24)
    - Conference on Cities,1971, Folder 2 of 2 (Box AO-25)
    - Committee on State and Local Government Corporation,1972, 6 folders (Box AO-25)
    - Committee on State and Local Government Corporation,1972-1973 and undated (Box AO-26)
    - Congress of African Peoples,1971 (Box AO-26)
    - Congress of Racial Equality,1963-1965 (Box AO-26)
    - Congress on Civil Rights, 1946 (Box AO-26)
    - Congressional Black Caucus,1971-1982 and undated, 3 folders (Box AO-26)
    - Consortium of Colleges and Universities,1968 (Box AO-26)
    - Continental Africa Chamber of Commerce,1979-1982 and undated, Folders 1-2 of 7 (Box AO-26)
    - Continental Africa Chamber of Commerce,1979-1982 and undated, Folders 2-7 of 7 (Box AO-27)
    - Coordinating Council for Senior Citizens,1980 (Box AO-27)
    - Cornell University, 1964, 1978 (Box AO-27)
    - Corporate Support Committee,1965 (Box AO-27)
    - Corporation for the Advancement of Experiential Learning Programs,1968-1983 and undated, 3 folders (Box AO-28)
    - Council for a Livable World,1964 (Box AO-28)
    - Council on Religion and International Affairs,1965-1968 (Box AO-28)
    - Cow-Country Commentary,1964 (Box AO-28)
    - Cyclopedia of Insurance in the United States,1957 (Box AO-28)
    - Dag Hammarskjold Foundation,1963-1964, and undated (Box AO-28)
    - Dedication of the Magnolia Ernest Recreational Complex,1977 (Box AO-28)
    - Defense Orientation Conference Association,1967-1969 (Box AO-28)
    - Democratic Convention,1978 (Box AO-28)
    - Democratic National Committee,1948-1973 (Box AO-28)
    - Democratic Party/National Convention,1980-1981 (Box AO-29)
    - Dillard University,1959 (Box AO-29)
    - District Court. Juvenile Division, 1971 (Box AO-29)
    - Division of World Mission Support,1961 (Box AO-29)
    - Donelain Pharmaceuticals, Inc.,1967 (Box AO-29)
    - Doremus and Company,1964 (Box AO-29)
    - Downtown Development Association,1960-1965 and undated (Box AO-29)
    - The Duke Endowment,1978 (Box AO-29)
    - Duke Power Company, 1979 (Box AO-29)
    - Duke University
      - Comprehensive Cancer Center,1982 (Box AO-29)
      - Divinity School. Board of Visitors,1960-1968 (Box AO-29)
      - General information,1966-1978 (Box AO-29)
      - Medical Center,1979-1983 (Box AO-29)
    - Dunne's Reports etc.,1956-1961 (Box AO-29)
    - Durham Arts Council, 1980 (Box AO-29)
    - Durham Boys Choir, 1976 (Box AO-29)
    - Durham Business and Professional Chain, 1941-1981 (Box AO-29)
    - Durham Business College, 1969 (Box AO-29)
    - Durham Centennial,1952-1953 (Box AO-29)
    - Durham (N.C.). Chamber of Commerce,1954-1982, 6 folders (Box AO-30)
    - Durham Chapter of Squaws, Inc., 1982 (Box AO-30)
    - Durham: Child First,1978-1979 (Box AO-30)
    - Durham City Schools,1967-1968 (Box AO-30)
    - Durham College,1977-1978 (Box AO-30)
    - Durham Committee on the Affairs of Black People,1979-1982, 2 folders (Box AO-30)
    - Durham Committee on Human Relations,1964-1967 (Box AO-30)
    - Durham Committee for Law and Justice, 1969-1970 (Box AO-31)
    - Durham Committee on Negro Affairs, 1947-1967, 2 folders (Box AO-31)
    - Durham Community Planning Council, 1964 (Box AO-31)
    - Durham Community and War Fund,1943-1946 (Box AO-31)
    - Durham Council on Human Relations, 1964 (Box AO-31)
    - Durham County Centennial Commission,1980-1981 (Box AO-31)
    - Durham County/City Schools,1978-1979 (Box AO-31)
    - Durham County (N.C.). Board of Commissioners,1968-1982 and undated, Folders 1-4 of 13 (Box AO-31)
    - Durham County (N.C.). Board of Commissioners,1968-1982 and undated, Folders 5-13 of 13 (Box AO-32)
    - Durham County (N.C.). Board of Commissioners, Campaign for,1954 (Box AO-32)
    - Durham County Community Mental Health Center,1968 (Box AO-32)
    - Durham County Democratic Convention,1983 (Box AO-32)
    - Durham County Democratic Executive Committee,1980-1981 (Box AO-33)
    - Durham County Department of Public Welfare,1968 (Box AO-33)
    - Durham County Health Department,1969-1981, 2 folders (Box AO-33)
    - Durham County Heart Association,1965 (Box AO-33)
    - Durham County Hospital Corporation, 1978-1979 (Box AO-33)
    - Durham County Library,1982-1983 (Box AO-33)
    - Durham County TB and Health Association, Inc.,1954 (Box AO-33)
    - Durham County Young Democrats,1980 (Box AO-33)
    - Durham Good Neighbor Drive,1935 (Box AO-33)
    - Durham Housing Authority, undated (Box AO-33)
    - Durham Interracial Goodwill Group,1948-1958 (Box AO-33)
    - Durham Interracial Goodwill Group. Clippings,1955-1958 (Box AO-33)
    - Durham Investment Corporation,1965 (Box AO-33)
    - Durham Junior Chamber of Commerce,1964 (Box AO-33)
    - DurhamโMiscellaneous,1959-1968 (Box AO-33)
    - DurhamโOrange County Heart Association,1953-1957 (Box AO-33)
    - Durham Technical Institute, 1978 (Box AO-33)
    - Durham Voters' Alliance,1977 (Box AO-33)
    - Durham's Committee of 100,1954-1965 (Box AO-33)
    - Durham's Interim Committee,1963 (Box AO-33)
    - Durham Youth Board,1956 (Box AO-33)
    - Educational Conference,1965 (Box AO-33)
    - Educational Testing Service,1968 (Box AO-33)
    - Ecumenical Institute,1967 (Box AO-33)
    - Elizabeth City State College,1968-1969 (Box AO-33)
    - Emancipation Centennial Celebration,1963 (Box AO-33)
    - The Emergency Land Fund,1979-1982 (Box AO-33)
    - Epilepsy Foundation, undated (Box AO-33)
    - Episcopal Church,1968 (Box AO-33)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission,1964-1965 (Box AO-33)
    - Executive Air Service,1960-1961, 2 folders (Box AO-33)
    - Executive Career Development, Inc.,1964 (Box AO-33)
    - Fair Employment Practice Committee,1945 (Box AO-34)
    - Family Service, Inc.,1956-1958 (Box AO-34)
    - Farleigh Dickinson University,1968-1970 (Box AO-34)
    - Father of the Year,1975 (Box AO-34)
    - Feature Broadcasting System, Inc.,1959 (Box AO-34)
    - Food and Agricultural Organization of the United Nations,1965 (Box AO-34)
    - Forbes,1964 (Box AO-34)
    - Ford Foundation,1961-1971 and undated, 3 folders (Box AO-34)
    - Foreign Policy Association,1958-1968 (Box AO-34)
    - Forty Club,1970 (Box AO-34)
    - Foster Business, Inc.,1960 (Box AO-34)
    - Foundation for Better Health of Durham,1977-1983 (Box AO-34)
    - Foundation for Community Development, Inc.,1968 (Box AO-34)
    - Foundation for Human Resource Development, Inc.,1967-1969, 2 folders (Box AO-35)
    - Foundation Library Center,1963 (Box AO-35)
    - Free People Foundation,1969 (Box AO-35)
    - Friends of Africa and America,1961-1964 (Box AO-35)
    - Friends of Duke Chapel,1982-1983 (Box AO-35)
    - Friends of LBJ Library,1980-1981 (Box AO-35)
    - Friends of Sam Moore Committee,1971 and undated (Box AO-35)
    - Friends of Duke University Library,1980-1982 (Box AO-35)
    - Friends of the Durham Library, Inc., undated (Box AO-35)
    - Freedoms Foundation at Valley Forge,1959-1972 (Box AO-35)
    - Fong Testimonial Committee,1963 (Box AO-35)
    - Fund for Scientific Education, Inc.,1971-1972, 2 folders (Box AO-35)
    - Gamma Iota Sigma Insurance Organization,1981 (Box AO-35)
    - General Baptist State Convention of North Carolina,1965 (Box AO-35)
    - General Electric,1963-1970, 3 folders (Box AO-35)
    - General Motors Corporation,1961-1968 (Box AO-36)
    - Ghana Today,1959 (Box AO-36)
    - Girl Scout Council of Greater New York, Inc.,1978-1980 (Box AO-36)
    - Goodwill Industries of America, Inc.,1966 (Box AO-36)
    - Governor's Advisory Council for State Technical Services Program for North Carolina,1966-1969, 4 folders (Box AO-36)
    - Governor's Agricultural-Industrial Tour of North Carolina,1965 and undated, 2 folders (Box AO-36)
    - Governor's Agricultural-Industrial Tour of North Carolina. Printed Material,1959-1965, Folder 1 of 3 (Box AO-36)
    - Governor's Agricultural-Industrial Tour of North Carolina. Printed Material,1959-1965, Folders 2-3 of 3 (Box AO-37)
    - Governor's Committee for Promotion of Employment for Veterans,1971-1973, 2 folders (Box AO-37)
    - W.T. Grant Company,1965-1972, Folders 1-4 of 5 (Box AO-37)
    - W.T. Grant Company,1965-1972, Folder 5 of 5 (Box AO-38)
    - Greater Organization for Divine Television (GOD-TV),1974 (Box AO-38)
    - Greensboro College,1983 (Box AO-38)
    - Hampton Institute,1963-1967 (Box AO-38)
    - Harris, Upham, & Company,1964-1968 (Box AO-38)
    - Hawkins Campaign Fund,1968 (Box AO-38)
    - Historic Figures, Inc., 1968-1980, Folders 1-4 of 6 (Box AO-38)
    - Historic Figures, Inc., 1968-1980, Folders 5-6 of 6 (Box AO-39)
    - Hollywood Beach Idea Bulletin,1964 (Box AO-39)
    - Holy Land State Committee,1978 (Box AO-39)
    - Housing Affairs Letter,1964 (Box AO-39)
    - Howard University
      - Addresses byJohn Hope Franklin, 1961, 1968 (Box AO-39)
      - Clippings,1962-1972 (Box AO-39)
      - Correspondence,1943-1954, 1961-1970, 1975-1983 and undated, 4 folders (Box AO-39)
    - Index Publishing Company,1953-1960 (Box AO-40)
    - Information Services Corporation,1968-1973 (Box AO-40)
    - Institute for American Democracy,1966-1968 (Box AO-40)
    - Institute for Black Elected Officials, 1969 (Box AO-40)
    - Institute for International Education, 1964 (Box AO-40)
    - Institute for Regional Development,1967 (Box AO-40)
    - Institute for the Study of Economic Systems,1968-1969 (Box AO-40)
    - Institute of Home Office Underwriters,1962 (Box AO-40)
    - The Institute of Mathematical Statistics,1946-1961 (Box AO-40)
    - Institute of the Black World,1971 (Box AO-40)
    - Institute on Retirement Planning,1959 (Box AO-40)
    - Insurance Hall of Fame,1978-1983, 2 folders (Box AO-40)
    - The Intelligence Digest Service,1964 (Box AO-40)
    - International African Chamber of Commerce,1971-1972 (Box AO-40)
    - International Association of Fire Fighters,1971 (Box AO-41)
    - International Business Machines Corporation,1946-1980 (Box AO-41)
    - International Businessmen's Who's Who, undated (Box AO-41)
    - International Conference on Housing, Housing Finance, and Housing Techniques,1966 (Box AO-41)
    - International Congress of Actuaries,1957 (Box AO-41)
    - International Executive Service Corps,1976-1979 (Box AO-41)
    - The International Platform Association,1967-1983 (Box AO-41)
    - International Yearbook and Statesman's Who's Who, 1961-1964 (Box AO-41)
    - Interracial Council for Business Opportunities,1964-1971 (Box AO-41)
    - Interstate Citizens Committee for Nixon,1960 (Box AO-41)
    - Iowa Wesleyan College,1968 (Box AO-41)
    - The Jamaica Progressive League, Inc.,1978 (Box AO-41)
    - James E. Shepard Memorial Foundation, Inc., 3 folders (Box AO-41)
    - Jet Magazine. Articles,1956 (Box AO-42)
    - John Avery Boys' Club,1929-1980 and undated, 3 folders (Box AO-42)
    - John Birch Society,1968 (Box AO-42)
    - John Liner Letter,1965 (Box AO-42)
    - Johnson C. Smith University,1967-1982, 3 folders (Box AO-42)
    - Joint Appropriations Committee,1965 (Box AO-43)
    - Joint Center for Political Studies,1972-1982 (Box AO-43)
    - Joint Civilian Orientation Conference,1966-1967, 3 folders (Box AO-43)
    - Joint Negro Appeal,1971 (Box AO-43)
    - Junior Achievement,1965-1967 (Box AO-44)
    - Junior League of Durham, Inc.,1979 (Box AO-44)
    - Kennedy Memorial Library,1964 (Box AO-44)
    - Khang Jen School, Taiwan, undated (Box AO-44)
    - Klein Institute for Aptitude Testing, Inc.,1964 (Box AO-44)
    - Koinonia Farm, Americus, Ga.,1966 (Box AO-44)
    - Law and Justice Committee,1971 (Box AO-44)
    - Lawrence H. Douglas and Co., Inc.,1964 (Box AO-44)
    - Lawrence-Leiter and Co.,1964 (Box AO-44)
    - Laymen's National Bible Committee, Inc.,1968-1970 (Box AO-44)
    - Leadership Conference on Civil Rights,1967-1971 (Box AO-44)
    - League of Women Voters,1959-1969 (Box AO-44)
    - League of Women Voters of North Carolina, 1982 (Box AO-44)
    - LeTourneau College, 1953-1970 (Box AO-44)
    - Life Office Management Association, 1948 and undated, 2 folders (Box AO-44)
    - Lincoln Community Health Center,1982 and undated (Box AO-44)
    - Lincoln Hospital,1943-1971, 5 folders (Box AO-45)
    - Local Committee for Equal Participation in Business, undated (Box AO-45)
    - Logan, Maud E. District Plans for 1980 (Box AO-45)
    - Lombard, Vitalis, and Paganucci, Inc.,1964 (Box AO-45)
    - Long Marketing, Inc.,1970 (Box AO-45)
    - Man and Manager, Inc.,1964 (Box AO-45)
    - Management Consultant,1965 (Box AO-45)
    - Management Improvement Corporation of America (MICA),1980-1982, Folder 1 of 4 (Box AO-45)
    - Management Improvement Corporation of America (MICA),1980-1982, Folders 2-4 of 4 (Box AO-46)
    - March of Dimes,1961-1964 (Box AO-46)
    - Marquis Who's Who,1960-1965 (Box AO-46)
    - Marshall and Stevens, Inc.,1964 (Box AO-46)
    - Martin Luther King, Jr. Center for Social Change,1980-1983 (Box AO-46)
    - Masonic Lodge,1965-1968 (Box AO-46)
    - Maupintour Associates,1959-1962, 1973-1983, 3 folders (Box AO-47)
    - Mayor's Committee on Human Relations, 1934-1971 and undated, Folders 1-7 of 10 (Box AO-48)
    - Mayor's Committee on Human Relations, 1934-1971 and undated, Folders 8-10 of 10 (Box AO-49)
    - Mechanics and Farmers Bank,1929-1983 and undated, Folders 1-5 of 10 (Box AO-49)
    - Mechanics and Farmers Bank,1929-1983 and undated, Folders 6-10 of 10 (Box AO-50)
    - Medical Information Bureau Executive Committee,1965 (Box AO-50)
    - Men and Management,1963-1965 (Box AO-50)
    - Metal Building Manufacturers Association,1965 (Box AO-50)
    - Metropolitan Opera,1965-1966 (Box AO-50)
    - Metropolitan Women's Democratic Club,1968 (Box AO-50)
    - Michelman and Hanf,1964-1965 (Box AO-50)
    - Michigan State University,1968 (Box AO-50)
    - Mid-Atlantic Title VI Conference,1965 (Box AO-50)
    - Minority Enterprise Small Business Investment Corporation (MESBIC),1978-1982 (Box AO-51)
    - Miss American Teenager,1971 (Box AO-51)
    - Morris College,1965 (Box AO-51)
    - Mortgage Company of Durham,1938-1941 (Box AO-51)
    - Mutual Savings and Loan Association,1930-1980, Folders 1-7 of 9 (Box AO-51)
      Earlier name: Mutual Building and Loan Association.
    - Mutual Savings and Loan Association,1930-1980, Folders 8-9 of 9 (Box AO-52)
    - Napoleon Hill Foundation,1968-1969 (Box AO-52)
    - Nathaniel Hill and Associates,1964 (Box AO-52)
    - The Nation, 1965 (Box AO-52)
    - National Ad Hoc U.S.O. Survey Committee,1961-1963 and undated, Folders 1-9 of 14 (Box AO-52)
    - National Ad Hoc U.S.O. Survey Committee,1961-1963 and undated, Folders 10-14 of 14 (Box AO-53)
    - National Afro-American Memorial Library Committee,1969 (Box AO-53)
    - National Assembly for Social Policy and Development, Inc.,1961-1967, Folders 1-2 of 3 (Box AO-53)
    - National Assembly for Social Policy and Development, Inc.,1961-1967, Folder 3 of 3 (Box AO-54)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP),1943-1974 and undated Oct., Folders 1-4 of 16 (Box AO-54)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP),1943-1974 and undated, Folders 5-9 of 16 (Box AO-55)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP),1943-1974 and undated, Folders 10-14 of 16 (Box AO-56)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP),1943-1974 and undated, Folders 15-16 of 16 (Box AO-57)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People Legal Defense and Educational Fund,1975-1983, 3 folders (Box AO-57)
    - National Association for Community Development,1968 (Box AO-57)
    - National Association of Insurance Commissioners,1961 (Box AO-57)
    - National Association of Intergroup Relations Officials,1953 (Box AO-57)
    - National Association of Manufacturers,1967 (Box AO-57)
    - National Association for the Southern Poor (NASP),1975 (Box AO-57)
    - National Bankers Association,1980-1981 (Box AO-57)
    - National Business League,1947-1959 (Box AO-58)
    - National Cash Register Co., 1957-1964 and undated (Box AO-58)
    - The National Caucus on the Black Aged, Inc.,1977-1981, 2 folders (Box AO-58)
    - National Center of Afro-American Artists, 1966-1971 and undated (Box AO-59)
    - National Center on the Black Aged,1979-1980, 2 folders (Box AO-59)
    - National Citizens' Committee for Community Relations,1964-1967, 2 folders (Box AO-59)
    - National Citizens' Committee,1965 (Box AO-59)
    - National Committee Against Discrimination in Housing,1961-1970 (Box AO-59)
    - National Committee for Peace with Freedom in Vietnam,1967 (Box AO-59)
    - National Committee on Tithing in Investment,1965 (Box AO-59)
    - National Conference of Catholic Charities,1968 (Box AO-59)
    - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1959-1983 and undated, Folder 1 of 17 (Box AO-59)
    - National Conference of Christians and Jews,1959-1983 and undated, Folders 2-8 of 17 (Box AO-60)
    - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1959-1983 and undated, Folders 9-14 of 17 (Box AO-61)
    - National Conference of Christians and Jews,1959-1983 and undated, Folders 15-17 of 17 (Box AO-62)
    - National Conference of Christians and Jews: Charles Evans Hughes Award,1965-1983 (Box AO-62)
    - National Conference of Health, Welfare, and Pension Plans,1963-1964 (Box AO-62)
    - National Conference on Small Business,1961 (Box AO-62)
    - National Council of Catholic Men. National Convention,1963 (Box AO-62)
    - National Council of Negro Women,1954-1971 (Box AO-62)
    - National Council of Senior Citizens,1962 (Box AO-62)
    - National Council on Crime and Delinquency,1967-1969 (Box AO-62)
    - National Cystic Fibrosis Research Foundation,1965 (Box AO-62)
    - National Defense Executive Reserve,1956-1960 and undated Nov., Folders 1-2 of 4 (Box AO-62)
    - National Defense Executive Reserve,1956-1960 and undated, Folders 3-4 of 4 (Box AO-63)
    - National Democratic Party of Alabama,1971 (Box AO-63)
    - National Dividend Plan,1971 (Box AO-63)
    - National Education Association,1965 (Box AO-63)
    - National Foundation of Health, Welfare, and Pension Plans,1964-1966 (Box AO-63)
    - National Fund for Medical Education,1966 (Box AO-63)
    - National Home Life Assurance Company,1980 (Box AO-63)
    - National Industrial Conference Board
      - Correspondence,1955-1969 and undated, Folders 1-4 of 6 (Box AO-63)
    - National Industrial Conference Board (Box AO-64)
      - Correspondence,1955-1969 and undated, Folders 5-6 of 6 (Box AO-64)
      - Miscellany, 1961-1965 and undated (Box AO-64)
      - Press Releases,1962 (Box AO-64)
      - Printed Material
        - Conference Board Previews, 1962-1963 (Box AO-64)
        - Conference Board Record, 1961-1966 (Box AO-64)
        - Road Maps of Industry, 1962-1967, Folder 1 of 3 (Box AO-64)
    - National Industrial Conference Board (Box AO-65)
      - Printed Material
        - Road Maps of Industry, 1962-1967, Folders 2-3 of 3 (Box AO-65)
        - Selected Business Indicators, 1963-1966 (Box AO-65)
        - Weekly Desk Sheet of Business Trends, 1962-1966 July, Folders 1-3 of 4 (Box AO-65)
    - National Industrial Conference Board (Box AO-66)
      - Printed Material
        - Weekly Desk Sheet of Business Trends, 1962-1966, Folder 4 of 4 (Box AO-66)
        - General, 1955-1968 and undated, Folders 1-4 of 5 (Box AO-66)
    - National Industrial Conference Board (Box AO-67)
      - Printed Material
        - General,1955-1968 and undated, Folder 5 of 5 (Box AO-67)